

Julio David Hernández Segura

julio-david@hotmail.com

Phone number: 795580892

Profile

I'm David hernandez I was born in 14/01/1997, I love to think of myself as a passionate sports and order person who enjoys every single bit of the routine like sport work. As a technology enthusiast and lifelong learner, I do love studying new things learn new methods, working with a team.

I am a punctual and hardworking young person. I like working in team I am a good problem solver, I strive to achieve excellent standards in customer experience, with the knowledge that this ensures repeat business for any organization

Professional Experience

Logistics (events and Recreation officer) – University of Quindío, Colombia 2015 – 2020

- Organizing university activities in a fast-paced environment
- Managing child recreation activities
- Organizing events, awards ceremonies and degree sessions
- Ensuring event catering is scheduled and delivered on time
- Dealing with customer queries to ensure operational efficiency
- Exceeding customer expectations in order to maximize experience

Linen Porter-Dublin

- Assist and support the housekeeping department with linen, ensuring all products are delivered promptly and safely
- To clean departure and stay over rooms as required
- To assist with changing the water in the Jacuzzi rooms in the absence of Maintenance
- To clean the public areas on a regular basis
- To distribute the linen to various floors / rooms as needed
- Collecting linen and organizing it for collection
- To make rooms if is needed

House keeper – Hotel Charme torchio Ascona 08/2022 – 11/2022

- Collecting linen and organizing it for collection
- make rooms if is needed
- clean the public areas on a regular basis
- clean departure and stay over rooms as required

Education

2022 – current Software developer Full stack E commerce - University College Dublin

2015 – 2020 BA Electronic Engineering - University Quindío, Colombia

2012 – 2014 Bio medic Engineering - University UAN, Colombia

• Spanish: Native speaker (Spanish citizen)

• English: B2 (International business level standard)

• Italian: B2

Excellent references available on request